翻译：吃货丁小七  小英的小号  慕风夕
翻译：cerri  huaxin007  回风舞雪兮
校对：莫莫
时间轴：aaaBao  薛定谔的猫
总监：somehacker
后期：bongpong
拿着
Take it.
我们遇到了地...
I'll tell you what, we're having an earth...
开始说吧
Start talking.
我不确定信号能否传出去
Uh, I'm not sure if we're even on the air.
发生了一系列爆炸
Uh, this is a...a series of explosions...
爆炸新闻
这是重大事件  这是一起重大突发事件
this is a major incident. The emergency is a major incident.
有人看到了炫目的橙色光芒
Reported bright lights and an orange glow...
最新消息
流星陨落于德国引起恐慌
这是流星落地的瞬间
That was the moment the meteor hit.
情况不像大规模袭击
It does now appear to be a major attack.
汉堡预警
弗朗索瓦·奥朗德
法国总统
自五年前降落在汉堡市郊起
Since they landed outside Hamburg five years ago,
它们就不断地侵占欧洲
they have steadily advanced across Europe.
我们已付出数以百万计的伤亡  然而
We've suffered millions of casualties, and yet...
主要政府官员仍在继续疏散
The evacuation of key government officials continuing.
即时消息
直播
毁灭横扫欧洲
已经成功阻止了它们的攻势
Has been able to stop their advance.
欧洲付出了最为惨重的生命代价
In human costs, the Europeans have paid the highest price.
英国伦敦     直播     法国巴黎
变种破坏了巴黎路障
能够模仿甚至预测我们的行动
the ability to mimic and even anticipate our actions.
如果我们不能在法国打败它们
If we do not defeat them in France,
我们就得在伦敦  纽约然后东京的街头
we'll be fighting them in the streets of London,
与之作战
then New York, then Tokyo.
入侵五周年新军事计划
突发新闻
全人类都面临威胁
All of humanity's at stake.
突发新闻
布里格姆将军
联合防御中心指挥官
五年之后我们终于赢得了一场胜利
After five years, we finally have a victory.
这些是刚从凡尔登发回的图片
These pictures are just in from Verdun.
值得注意的是  联军的胜利
Striking things about the quick coalition victory
付出了极小的伤亡和代价
was how low casualties were and how little damage...
我们今天收获了一场出色的胜利
We have seen a stunning victory here today.
联军重新夺回了凡尔登
The united defense force has retaken Verdun.
让·布里格姆: 我们能赢
凡尔登之后新战略
你如何让人们相信我们能赢得胜利
How do you convince people that this is a fight that can be won?
这是一场全球范围内的外星入侵
This is an alien invasion in a global war.
借助新的护甲技术和有限训练
With the new jacket technology and limited amount of training,
我们发明了超级士兵
we've been able to create super-soldiers.
威廉姆·凯奇少校
美国军方媒体公关
参军人数增加
请看丽塔·薇拉塔斯基  凡尔登天使
Look at Rita Vrataski, the angel of Verdun.
他们称她为凡尔登天使
They're calling her the angel of Verdun.
她被看做这场战争新的希望
She is seen as the new hope for this war.
真是非同凡响
It's extraordinary.
借助新的护甲技术和有限训练
With the new jacket technology and limited training,
丽塔·薇拉塔斯基第一天开始战斗
Rita Vrataski was able to kill
就成功杀死了几百个变种
hundreds of mimics on only her first day in combat.
一种革命式的新技术
A revolutionary new technology...
还需要你的加入
The only thing missing is you.
联合防御中心
没有你们的参与我们就没有明天
她杀掉了几百个变种
She's killed hundreds of mimics.
她在开始战斗的第一天
She was able to kill hundreds of mimics
事态进展
威廉姆·凯奇少校
就能够杀掉几百个变种
on only her first day in combat.
想象一支由很多丽塔·薇拉塔斯基组成的军队
Imagine an army of Rita Vrataskis.
我们成功将它们逼回英吉利海峡
We're managing to hold them back at the English channel,
即时消息
没落行动进入倒数
[二战末期盟军酝酿对日本本土的进攻计划]
-但是能坚持多久呢  -现在下结论还为时尚早
- but for how long? - This is dangerous talk
民众的怀疑很容易理解
and it's easy to understand why people are suspicious...
有大约70个国家加入了联军
about 70 nations have joined the united defense force,
希望能够永远击退它们
which hopes to push them back once and for all.
我们已经掌控了局面
We've got 'em contained.
有了这项新技术  我们肯定能打败它们
And with this new technology, we're gonna defeat 'em.
没落行动将成为人类历史上
Operation downfall is going to be the largest
最大型的机械化侵袭
mechanized invasion in the history of mankind.
我们会胜利的
We will be victorious.
我们要做的就是战斗
We fight. That's what we do.
伦敦
威廉姆·凯奇少校  美国军方媒体公关
Major William Cage, United States military media.
欢迎来到伦敦  少校
Welcome to London, Major.
联合防御中心总部
将军现在要见你
The General will see you now.
谢谢
Thank you.
没落行动
Operation downfall.
联军的全部力量将从法国
The entire might of the UDF, invading from France,
地中海以及斯堪的纳维亚进入
the Mediterranean, Scandinavia,
以缓解东部前线的压力
relieving pressure on the eastern front,
为俄罗斯和中国提供机会击退敌人
allowing the Russians and Chinese to push the enemy back.
我们将在中部会和
We all meet in the middle,
沿途消灭变种这一祸害
exterminating this mimic scourge along the way.
明天会有很多优秀的士兵牺牲  少校
A lot of good soldiers are gonna die tomorrow, Major.
当硝烟散尽
You know, when the smoke clears
遗体被送回家乡
and the body bags start coming home,
人们将寻找替罪羊
people tend to look for someone to blame,
像我这样的人
someone like me.
我理想的是另外一种情景
Ideally, I'd prefer a different scenario.
请
Please.
比如一本畅销的回忆录什么的
A best-selling memoir, perhaps.
或者进入政界
Maybe a career in politics?
我第一个想到的是
Off the top of my head,
把一切说成是天赋使命
I would go with the-the sense of manifest destiny.
白手起家  青云直上
Rags to riches. Rapid rise through the ranks.
注定来拯救我们
Uh, born to deliver us.
人们喜欢这种东西
And the people...well, they love that sort of thing.
你想错了  少校
You misunderstand, Major.
我不是让你来宣传我的
I didn't ask you here to sell me.
我想让你宣传这次侵袭
I want you to sell the invasion.
好吧
Okay.
你一小时后坐船出发
You ship out for the coast in one hour.
摄影师随时待命
Your camera crew is standing by.
你会跟首轮进攻一起登陆海滩
You'll be on the beach with the first wave.
我没听错吧  首轮进攻
Uh, I'm sorry, the f-first wave?
海滩  你是说  前线吗
The beach? You mean...the front?
法国
France.
卫星显示海岸线敌人没什么动静
Satellites show minimal enemy movement on the coast.
几乎没有抵抗
Little resistance.
很激动吧  以后讲给你孙子听
A little excitement, something to tell your grandchildren.
我很欣赏
While I appreciate...
您的信心  将军
the confidence, General,
可我来就是为了避免这种情况的
that's... I'm do... I do this to avoid doing that.
这个
It's...
我大学进的是后备军官训练营
I... I... I was in ROTC in college.
战争爆发了
Uh, the war broke out,
我的广告公司倒闭了  我才来的
I lost my advertising firm and here I am.
我们各司其职
You know, I do what I do, and you-you do what you do.
但是
But...
我其实不是一个士兵
I'm not a...soldier, really.
不  你当然不是
No, of course you're not.
这就是为什么我把你
That's why I'm embedding you
跟几十万士兵放在一起
with several hundred thousand men and women who are.
这是一种荣幸  将军
While it is an honor, general,
可我恐怕必须谢绝了
I'm afraid I'm gonna have to decline.
我受不了血腥场面
Can't stand the sight of blood.
这又不是剪纸游戏
Not so much as a paper cut.
坐在这儿想一下
Uh, but, uh, si-sitting here thinking about this,
我脑子里已经有好几个名字
uh-uh-uh, a couple of names come to mind
我觉得可以推荐给您
that I feel I could recommend to you. It's...
这不是提议  少校  这是命令
It's not an offer, Major. It's an order.
将军  我是美国军方的军官
General, I am an officer in the United States' military.
你甚至没有权力命令我
You don't even have the authority.
我跟你的指挥官说过了
I have spoken to your C.O.
你现在归我管
You are now under my command.
当然  你能保持现在的军衔
You will retain your present rank, of course.
我秘书那里有详细资料
My secretary has all the details.
好好干  少校
Do a good job, Major.
祝你好运  你可以走了
Good luck. You are dismissed.
将军
General?
我刚刚鼓舞了上百万人
I just inspired millions of people...
来加入你的军队
to join your army.
可是当尸体被运回家乡时
And when the body bags come home,
人们将寻找替罪羊
and they're looking for someone to blame...
你觉得对我来说
How hard do you think it would be
说服人们归罪于你会有多难
for me to convince people to blame you?
我想将军您应该不希望这样
I'd imagine that the general would prefer to avoid that.
你在威胁我吗  少校
Are you blackmailing me, Major?
我更希望
I would prefer...
明天可以不用去前线
not to be filming acts of heroism and valor
拍摄那些英勇的事迹
on that beach tomorrow.
你不用去
You won't be.
很高兴我们能解决这个问题
I'm glad we could, uh, work this out.
如果可以的话  将军  我...
Now if you'll excuse me, General, I...
谢谢
Thank you.
抓住这个人
Arrest this man.
什么
What?
停下
Stop right there!
喂  停下
Hey! Stop!
抓住他
Hold it!
左翼  前进
Left flank, march!
向后  转
About-turn!
供应于十分钟后结束
Supplies closing in ten minutes.
排好队
Get yourselves in line!
西斯罗机场
加入机械战队
全金属婊子
站起来  你这废物
On your feet, maggot!
不该对长官这样说话  军士
That is no way to address an officer, Sergeant.
我就是这么跟一个呆瓜新兵说话的
It's how I address a slack-jawed recruit
然后我会拿鞋跟捅烂他的屁眼  废物
right before I bust his hole with my boot heel, maggot.
等一下  军士
Hold up there, Sergeant.
有什么能帮你的吗  先生
Can I help you, sir?
我到底在哪里  军士
Where the hell am I, Sergeant?
前沿作战基地西斯罗机场
Forward operating base Heathrow.
你刚和一群新兵一起来的
You just came in with the fresh recruits.
我看起来像新兵吗
Do I strike you as a fresh recruit?
不  先生  你不像
No, sir, you do not.
我是威廉姆·凯奇少校
My name is Major William Cage.
-我是一名美国军官  -军官
- I'm an American officer. - Officer?
这是新兵训练营
This is processing.
这里没有军官
There's no officers down here.
我来处理  军士
I got this, Sergeant.
你到底是怎么到新兵营来的
How the hell did you end up in processing?
是因为什么
What was it?
扑克之夜还是单身派对
Poker night? Bachelor party?
如果对你来说没有区别  军士
If it's all the same to you, Sergeant,
我希望能跟我在华盛顿的长官解释
I'd like to explain that to my commanding officer in Washington,
所以如果你能带我去打电话  我可以...
so if you'll just take me to a phone, I can...
你听到了吗
Haven't you heard?
我们正在紧急备战阶段
We're t-minus-haul-ass-h-hour.
我们正在整军准备入侵法国
We're fixing to invade France.
整个前沿作战基地都被封锁了
This whole F.O.B.'s on lockdown.
没有任何电话往来
No calls. In or out.
-你叫法雷利  -没错
- Your name is Farell. - That's right.
法雷利军士长
Master sergeant Farell.
法雷利军士长  你是一位美国人
Master sergeant Farell, you're an American.
不  长官  我来自肯塔基
No, sir. I'm from Kentucky.
好吧  看着我
Okay. Well, look at me.
看看我在什么地方
And look at where I am.
我是被强迫送来的
I've been railroaded.
很明显我不属于这里
It's obvious I don't belong here.
拜托了  中士
So please, Sergeant,
肯定有方法能打电话的
there has to be a way I can make a phone call.
我会解决你的问题的  长官
I'll get you sorted out, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
走这边
Right this way.
你从肯塔基哪里来的  军士长
Where you from in Kentucky, Sergeant?
一个叫科学山的小镇
Little town called Science Hill.
听说过吗
Heard of it?
现在听说了
I have now.
你呢  你从哪里来的
How 'bout you? Where you from?
克兰伯里[也译作蔓越莓]  新泽西
Cranbury, New Jersey.
他们种了不少蔓越莓  对吧
They grow a lot of cranberries there, do they?
番茄  最最好吃的番茄
Tomatoes. Best you ever had.
那为什么要叫克兰伯里[蔓越莓]呢
Why they call it Cranberry, then?
那他们为什么把它叫做科学山呢
Why they call it Science Hill?
从来没问过  我不关心
Never asked. Don't care.
您先走
After you.
你不是带我去打电话的对吧  军士长
You're not taking me to a phone, are you, sergeant?
不  我不是
No, I am not.
似乎目前为止你唯一说的实话
Seems about the only honest thing you said to me
是你的名字
so far is your name.
这里写着你是个逃兵
It says here you're a deserter.
写着你在伪装军官时被抓获
It says here you were caught impersonating an officer.
还写着你可能会尝试打出电话
It says here you'd likely try to make an outside call,
甚至不惜牺牲基地的安全
even compromise security of this operation.
绞尽脑汁逃避明天的作战任务
Anything to get out of combat duty tomorrow.
不过这些都不会发生
But that's not gonna happen.
绝无可能   二等兵凯奇
Ever...private Cage.
流言很可怕
Rumor is a terrible thing.
今晚之前  这些人都会知道
Come nightfall, these men will all reach the same conclusion.
你是个懦夫  还是个骗子
That you're a coward and a liar,
认为自己的命比他们的重要
putting your life above theirs.
好消息是你还有希望  二等兵
The good news is there's hope for you, private.
参与光荣的战斗
Hope in the form of glorious combat.
战斗是最伟大的救赎
Battle is the great redeemer.
是锤炼真英雄的浴火熔炉
The fiery crucible in which the only true heroes are forged.
唯一一个众生平等的地方
The one place where all men truly share the same rank,
不管他们本来是什么样的废物
regardless of what kind of parasitic scum they were going in.
注意了
Hey, yo!
队员们
Squad!
这位是二等兵凯奇
This here is private Cage.
二等兵凯奇  这里是J小队
Private Cage, J Squad.
那不是军官的制服吗
Isn't that an officer's uniform?
军官可不会用这样的袖扣
Those sure ain't officer cufflinks.
大家的早上都很充实嘛
I see everyone is havin' a productive mornin'.
这让我十分骄傲
You know, it gives me a swell of pride
有你们这样的精兵
knowin' soldiers of your...
去主导明天的战役
caliber will be leadin' the charge tomorrow.
锐如尖矛
Tip of the spear.
利如刀锋
Edge of the knife.
捅进了我的...屁眼
Crack of my...ass.
该死
Oh, shit.
二等兵基梅尔
Private Kimmel,
我是怎么看待在营房里赌博的
what is my view of gamblin' in the barracks?
你不喜欢  法雷利军士长
You dislike it, Sergeant Farell.
南希  我为什么不喜欢
Nance, why do I dislike it?
因为这会让我们觉得
'Cause it entertains the notion
我们的命运掌握在别人手里
that our fate is in hands other than our own.
我对于命运这个词
And what is my definitive position
是怎么定义的  一起说
on the concept of fate, chorus?
时刻准备  严守纪律
Through readiness and discipline,
命运由我们自己掌控
we are masters of our fate.
你可能会觉得这种观点十分讽刺
You might call that notion ironic.
不过相信我  你会接受的
But, trust me, you'll come around.
二等兵凯奇是一名逃兵
Private Cage is a deserter.
拯救他是你们所有人的责任
I'm making you all personally responsible for his deliverance.
明早六点他要做好战斗准备
He will be combat ready at oh-six-hundred tomorrow.
战斗准备
Combat ready?
二等兵凯奇身陷幻想中
Private Cage is under the delusion
觉得自己不属于这里
he does not belong here.
我们必须打破他的幻想
We must dissuade him of this delusion.
如果他尝试逃跑
If he tries to run,
你们完全可以把他打到生活不能自理
feel free to dissuade him until he can't piss standing up.
不  不  军士长  你必须听我说
No, no. Sergeant, you have to listen to me.
我永远无法做好战斗准备
I will never be combat ready.
我嫉妒你  凯奇
I envy you, Cage.
明早你就会受到洗礼的
Tomorrow morning, you will be baptized.
重获新生
Born again.
十分钟体能训练
P.T.! Ten minutes!
穿错制服了  二等兵
you're not in uniform, private.
所有备战妥当的中队
Could all combat-ready squadrons...
又是新的一天  同志们
It's a new day, people.
命运在召唤我们
Destiny calls.
全世界都期盼着我们能赢
The world expects only one thing from us that we will win.
地雷呢
Where's the claymores, please?
我的宝贝们呢
Where's my babies?
小心爆炸
克莱莫地雷
基梅尔  让我们一举拿下它
Come on, Kimmel, let's have it!
我的天啊  基梅尔
Oh, for Chris sake, Kimmel.
这样自在啊
I gotta be free, man!
好了  准备上战场
All right, man, let's get this show on the road.
我也得重装上阵了
I gotta suit up.
那是什么声音
What's that noise? That...
走吧
Let's go.
听我说  兄弟
Listen, man,
我从未穿过战甲
I've never been in one of these.
我也没试过
Yeah, well, I've never been with
同时跟两个女孩上床
two girls at the same time before.
但如果有机会
But you can bet when that day comes,
我一定能搞定
I'll make it work.
等等  基梅尔
Hey, hey, hey. Yeah, Kimmel...
我是格里夫
It's Griff.
格里夫  格里夫  我求你了
Griff. Griff. You bet.
你想想看
Just think about this, man.
我可能会用它伤害到别人
I could hurt somebody with...
开启安全模式就好了
Not with the safety on, you won't.
赶紧就位  兄弟
Get a shift on, mate. Come on!
准备好了吗
You ready?
安全模式在哪里开
Aw, Where is the safety?
非常正确
Exactly.
请勿穿行
时间到
It's time.
我的天  这不是全金属...
Bloody hell, it's the full metal b...
动起来
Move!
-格里夫  -军士长
- Griff. - Sarge?
照顾好二等兵凯奇
Take care of private Cage.
一整天吗
What, all day?
我的直觉告诉我  不用那么久
Somethin' tells me it won't be nearly that long.
出发吧
Let's go!
格里夫  凯奇
Griff! Cage!
-凯奇  -凯奇
- Cage! - Cage!
我们失去了德国
We lost Germany.
失去了法国
We lost France.
如果今天再输
If we lose today,
就不用再打了
we won't get to fight another.
我知道你们的压力很大
I know the pressure on you is enormous.
两分钟后空降
Two minutes to drop.
害怕是正常的
It's all right to be scared.
记住  没有恐惧就没有勇气
Remember there's no courage without fear.
伙计
Oi, mate!
你的战甲好像有点问题
I think there's something wrong with your suit.
对  有个死人在里面
Yeah. There's a dead guy in it.
下去后管好自己  先生
Hey, watch your back out there. Sir.
没人会管你
No one else will.
一分钟
One minute!
一分钟后空降
One minute to drop!
干嘛
What?
我怎么把武器的安全模式打开
How do I turn the safety off of my weapon?
什么
What?!
我要怎么把武器的安全模式...
How do I turn the safety off...
天啊
Oh, my god!
准备
Get ready!
30秒后空降
Thirty seconds to drop!
听我的指令
On my mark!
做好空降准备
Stand by to deploy!
拉好空降索
Activate drop lines.
记住
Remember...
跳
Drop!
赶紧跳
Drop! Drop!
快跳
Drop!
快
Go!
赶紧跳
Go, let's go!
抓紧时间
Come on!
跳  快跳
Drop! Drop!
凯奇  要么跳要么死
Cage! Drop or die!
我们成功了
We made it!
感谢上帝  我们成功了
Thank God, we made it!
选择语言
Select language.
快走
Let's move it!
我们需要支援
We need help!
请求立即支援
Someone help us out! We need it now!
我的
What the...
二等兵凯奇
Private Cage!
你走错方向了
You goin' the wrong way.
你会想念这一刻的
You're gonna miss your moment.
什么情况啊
What the hell?
它们不应该知道我们会来的
They're not supposed to know we're even coming.
我们这是进了屠宰场啊
We walked into a slaughterhouse, man.
简直就是屠宰场
It's a slaughterhouse!
振作起来  福特
Pull yourself together, Ford!
动起来  兄弟们
On your feet, people!
调整好队形
Get in line!
南希  报告下战况
Nance, get me a sit-rep.
-安全模式  -格里夫  福特守住侧面
- Safety! - Griff, Ford, cover the flank!
安全模式  安全模式
My safety! My safety.
我要怎么调到安全模式
How do I get my safety?
-南希  快点  -追踪到了
- I'm waitin', Nance! - I got traces!
在五百米以外  它们的速度很快
Five hundred meters and they're coming in fast!
狗日的
Sumbitch.
别挡路
Get outta the way!
想活下来就给我列好队
Look alive if you wanna stay that way!
射击就位
Firing positions!
它们来了
Here they come.
来势汹汹  数量惊人
Mean as hell and thick as grass.
等它们再靠近点
Wait till they're right on us.
再过几秒
A few more seconds.
格里夫  后退
Griff, fall back!
重载
Reload.
左右左
Left, right, left!
全金属婊子
加入机械战队
站起来  你这废物
On your feet, maggot!
在我拿鞋跟捅烂你的
Get in line before I bust your hole
屁眼前站好队  废物
with my boot heel, maggot!
让我来  军士长
Hold up there, sergeant.
有什么能帮到你的吗  先生
Can I help you, sir?
法雷利军士长
Sergeant Farell.
这是
Is it...?
那是我的名字
That is my name.
我想我知道了
I think I get it.
怎么回事
What was it?
扑克之夜
Poker night?
还是单身派对
Bachelor party?
我也不知道
You know, I'm not sure.
常有的事
It happens.
我会帮你安排好的  先生
I'll get you sorted out, sir.
让我帮你拿吧
Let me take those for you.
今天是几号
What... What day is it?
对于你来说吗
For you?
审判日
Judgment day.
你还是有希望的  二等兵
The good news is there's hope for you, private.
参与光荣的战斗
Hope in the form of glorious combat.
战斗是最伟大的救赎
Battle is the great redeemer,
是锤炼
the fiery crucible
-真英雄的浴火  -真英雄的浴火
- in which the only true heroes - in which the only true heroes
熔炉
are forged.
你刚刚是在打断我吗  二等兵
Did you just interrupt me, private?
军士长  你
Sarge, you're...
你绝对不会相信
You're... you're not gonna believe
我接下来要说的话
what I'm about to tell you.
当然不信
No, I'm not.
我讲到哪里了
Now, where was I?
是锤炼
The fiery crucible...
The fiery crucible
真英雄的浴火熔炉
in which the only true heroes are forged.
唯一一个众生平等的地方
The one place where all men truly share the same rank,
不管他们本来是什么样的废物
regardless of what kind of parasitic scum they were goin' in.
欢迎来到地狱  亲爱的
Welcome to hell, honey.
队员们  这个是二等兵凯奇
Squad! This here is private Cage.
二等兵凯奇
Private Cage.
这里是J小队
J squad.
那不是军官的制服吗
Isn't that an officer's uniform?
军官可不会用这样的袖扣
They sure ain't officer cufflinks.
我十分骄傲
You know, it gives me a swell of pride
知道有你们这样的精兵
knowing soldiers of your...
去主导明天的战役
Caliber will be leadin' the charge tomorrow.
锐如尖矛  锋如刀刃
Tip of the spear, edge of the knife,
捅进了我的屁眼
crack of my ass.
二等兵基梅尔  我怎么看待在营房里赌博的
Private Kimmel, what is my view of gamblin' in the barracks?
很反感  法雷利中士
Dislike it, sergeant Farell.
南希  我为什么反感
Nance, why do I dislike it?
因为这会让我们觉得
Because it entertains the notion
我们的命运受他人掌控
that our fate is in hands other than our own.
我对命运这个词
And what is my definitive position
是怎么定义的  一起说
on the concept of fate, Chorus?
时刻准备  严守纪律
Through readiness and discipline,
命运由我们自己掌控
we are masters of our fate.
你可能会觉得这种观点十分讽刺
You might call that notion ironic.
相信我  你会接受的
Trust me, you'll come around.
我的天啊  基梅尔
Oh, for Chris sake, Kimmel.
这样自在啊
I gotta be free, man!
好了  准备上战场
All right, man, let's get this show on the road.
我也得重装上阵了
I gotta suit up.
走吧
Let's go.
分离
Disengaged.
你有毛病啊
Hey, what the hell's wrong with you, man?
你没穿过战甲吗
Haven't you ever been in one of these before?
也许吧
Maybe.
你知道安全模式在哪里开吗
Do you know where the safety is?
不确定
I'm not sure.
很好
Good.
我知道你们的压力很大
I know the pressure on you is enormous.
两分钟后空降
Two minutes to drop.
害怕是正常的
It's all right to be scared.
记住  没有恐惧就没有勇气
Remember there's no courage without fear.
伙计
Ey! Oi, mate!
你的战甲好像有点问题
I think there's something wrong with your suit.
对  有个死人在里面
Yeah. There's a dead guy in it.
下去后记得小心  先生
Hey, watch your back out there, sir.
没人会管你
No one else will.
我去  你个狗娘养的
Jinx, bitch!
听我的指令
On my mark!
做好空降准备
Stand by to deploy!
拉好空降索  30秒后空降
Activate drop lines, thirty seconds.
降到地上
Hit the street...
快跳  快跳
Go! Go!
天啊  我们成功了
Woo-hoo! We made it!
-感谢天  我们成功了  -小心后面
- Thank God, we made it! - Behind you!
小心
Look out!
来了
Incoming!
我受伤了  我受伤了
I'm hit. I'm hit.
有多严重
How bad is it?
流了很多血吗
Is there... is there a... a lot of blood?
你胸口上有个洞
You have a hole in your chest.
真的吗
Really?
你刚是拆了我的电池吗
Did you just take my...my battery...battery?
不  不  不
No, no, no, no.
我的天
Holy fuck!
左  右  左
Left, right, left.
站起来  你这废物
On your feet, maggot!
法雷利军士长
Sergeant Farell!
-法雷利军士长  -能帮你什么吗
- Sergeant Farell. - Can I help you, sir?
我是比尔·凯奇少校
My name is major Bill Cage.
美国军事演说家
I'm U.S. Army media relations.
我没有参加单身派对或者赌博
I was not at a bachelor party or a poker game.
你左边口袋有封指令
You have an order in your left pocket
说我冒充军官  作为一个逃犯被抓了
that says I'm a deserter caught impersonating an officer.
但里面没说你是
But what it doesn't say is that your...
你是法雷利军士长
your name is master sergeant Farell
来自肯塔基州的科学山镇
from Science Hill, Kentucky.
如果你能给我30秒
And if you'll give me thirty seconds
解释我为什么知道这些
to explain how I know that,
你也许就能拯救基地里的所有人
you may just save the lives of every soldier on this base.
你得听我说
You have to listen to me!
它们知道我们要偷袭
They know we're coming!
它们正等着我们
They're waiting for us!
我亲身经历过
I have been there!
亲眼看到过
I've seen it!
你们都得完蛋了
You're all doomed!
You're doomed!
好了好了  我没事了
Okay, okay, okay. Okay, I'm fine.
我没事
I'm fine.
这是J小队吧
This is j squad. Yes?
这是J小队
This is j squad, yes.
我本不应该知道的  不过没事
Not that I should know that, but okay.
你们之前有见过我吗
Have any of you met me before?
混蛋  我不认识你
Bitch, I don't know you.
很好  谢谢你
Exactly! Yes! Thank you.
你叫南希  你叫比布尔
Your name is Nance. You're Bibble.
基布尔  不  是基梅尔
Kibble... Kimmel!
你经常裸身上阵
You fight balls out. Literally.
福特  斯金纳  格里夫
Ford. Skinner. Griff.
你叫
You're...
他话很少
He doesn't talk much.
他们在床上玩牌
But there's a card game under the bed.
真是多谢你了  混蛋
Thanks a lot, asshole.
基梅尔有一手同花顺
Uh, Kimmel's working on a flush.
黑桃  不  是梅花
Uh, spades... no, clubs.
你将要逼他们吃掉这些纸牌
And you're gonna make them eat those cards.
我说得没错吧
Am I right?
听我说
Now...
接下来我要说的可能会很疯狂
What I'm about to tell you sounds crazy.
但都是真的
It's true.
你们得听我的
And you have to listen to me.
这是决定你们性命的时刻
Your very lives depend on it.
一分钟后空降
One minute!
飞船快要爆炸了
The ship is gonna explode!
The ship is about to explode!
他在说什么
What? What is he saying?
南希  他在说什么
Nance! What is he saying?
飞船快要爆炸了
The ship is about to explode!
有人听到我说话吗
Hey! Anyone!
听我的指令  准备空降
On my mark! Stand by to deploy!
-拉好空降索  -飞船要爆炸了
- Activate drop lines. - The ship is about to explode!
天啊  我们成功了
Yeah! Whoo! We made it!
感谢上帝  我们成功了
Thank god, we made it!
我会拿鞋跟捅烂你的屁眼
...before I bust your hole with my boot heel!
太好了  我们成功了
Yeah! Whoo! We made it!
感谢上帝  我们成功了
Thank god, we made it!
抱歉  我这是在救你
I'm sorry! I'm trying to save you.
我们将遭遇大屠杀
We're getting slaughtered.
你得带我们从海滩突围
You need to get us off this beach.
我们得快走
We have to go.
这艘沉船马上就要爆炸了
This drop ship is about to explode.
我们得马上离开
We have to go now.
等等
Wait.
快走
Come on!
快点啊
快走  这艘船马上就要爆炸了
Come on! This ship is going to explode!
你要干什么
What are you doing?!
苏醒后  记得来找我
Find me when you wake up.
-什么  -醒了来找我
- What?! - Come find me when you wake...
站起来  你这废物
On your feet, maggot!
在我拿鞋跟捅烂你的屁眼前
Get in line before I bust your hole
站好队  废物
with my boot heel, maggot!
你还是有希望的  二等兵
Good news is there's hope for you, private.
战斗是最伟大的救赎
Battle is the great redeemer.
是锤炼真英雄的浴火熔炉
The fiery crucible in which the only true heroes are forged.
唯一一个众生平等...
The one place where all men truly sh... share the...
队员们  这位是二等兵凯奇
Squad, this here is private Cage.
我是士兵凯奇  你们一定是J小队吧
Private Cage. And you must be J squad.
很高兴见到你们
It's good to meet you.
你穿的是军官服吗
Isn't that an officer's uniform?
-军官可不会...  -军官可不会用这样的袖扣
- Those sure ain't officer's... - These sure ain't officer's cuff links.
钥匙应该在
Keys in the...
左侧口袋
left pocket probably.
士兵凯奇是个逃兵
Private Cage is a deserter.
拯救他是你们
I'm making you all personally responsible
所有人的责任
for his deliverance.
明早六点他要做好战斗准备
He will be combat-ready by oh-six-hundred tomorrow.
二等兵凯奇身陷幻想中
Private Cage is under the delusion
觉得自己不属于这里
he does not belong here.
我们必须打破他的幻想
We must dissuade him of this delusion.
如果他尝试逃跑
If he tries to run,
-你们完全可以把他...   -不  不可能
- feel free to dissuade him until... - oh, no, no, no.
我不会背弃大家的
I'm... I'm not going to run from you guys.
这绝对不可能
It's... not a chance.
打到生活不能自理
Till he can't piss standin' up.
谢谢你  法雷利军士长
Thank you, sergeant Farell.
然后做什么  体能训练吗
What next? A little, P.T.?
体能训练  十分钟
P.T.! Ten minutes!
左
Left!
你们是谁  大声说
What are you?! Sound off!
是战士
I'm a warrior!
战士的天职是
What do warriors do?!
杀敌
Kill!
-战士的天职是  -杀敌
- What are you gonna do?! - Kill!
明天是我参加的第二十场战役了
It's gonna be my twentieth battle tomorrow, man.
你才没打那么多仗  老兄
You haven't been in twenty battles, mate.
-我也参战无数  -明天一登滩
- I have too. - You're gonna dump your load
你就得缴械投降
the second we hit the beach tomorrow.
你们俩快他妈闭嘴吧
Why don't you two get yourselves a nice hot cup
不吹牛能死啊
of shut-the-hell-up!
姑娘  你真有意思
You funny, girl.
你看着吧  我明天一定会创下纪录
But I bet you I set some kind of record tomorrow.
逃跑第一名  福特
Fastest time runnin' backwards, Ford...
被自己绊倒  摔个狗吃屎
Slippin' in your own shit.
杀敌
Kill!
停下站好
Knock off the grab-ass!
站好  军士
Grab this, Sarge!
停下
Hold up!
二等兵  趴下做俯卧撑
Private, drop and give me...
做50个  对吧  军士
Fifty, Sarge?!
没错
That's right.
50个俯卧撑
Fifty.
全排听命
Platoon!
趴下做50个俯卧撑
Drop and give me fifty!
点名表扬士兵凯奇
Compliments of private Cage.
谢谢  军士
Thank you, Sarge!
-一  -一
- And one! - One!
-二  -二
- And two! - Two!
-三  -三
- And three! - Three!
四
Four!
五  六
Five! Six!
七
Seven!
你他妈抽什么风
What the hell were you thinkin'?
你还有希望  二等兵
There's hope for you, private.
参与光荣的战斗
Hope in the form of glorious combat.
战斗是最伟大的救...
Battle is the great redeemer...
二
Two!
-三  -三
- Three! - Three!
-四  -四
- Four! - Four!
-五  -五
- Five! - Five!
六
Six!
七
Seven!
八
Eight!
九  十
Nine! Ten!
十一  十二
Eleven! Twelve!
十三  十四
Thirteen! Fourteen!
禁入
薇拉塔斯基中士
Excuse me. Sergeant Vrataski.
打扰一下
Excuse me!
薇拉塔斯基中士
Sergeant Vrataski!?
打扰一下
Excuse me!
什么事  谁允许你进来的
Yes? Who said you could talk to me?
我脸上有什么东西吗  大兵
Have I got something on my face, soldier?
你  你说过
You did. You did.
明天  在海滩
Tomorrow. At the beach.
明天的海滩上
我们见面
We meet.
你让我醒来后找你
You said to find you when I wake up.
你知道我在说什么
You do know what's happening to me.
跟我来
Come with me.
立刻
Now.
除了我  不要跟任何人提起这件事
You don't talk to anyone about this but me.
因为最好的情况是
'Cause the best case scenario
你被送进精神病院
is you're gonna end up in a psych ward.
最糟的是  被当成解剖研究对象
And the worst case, you'll get dissected for study.
-听懂了吗  明白吗  -明白
- Are we clear? Yes? - Yes.
你第一次死的时候  有什么事发生
First time you died, what happened?
-你杀死了一个变种  -是的
- You killed a mimic? - Yes.
说具体点
Describe it.
它长得很不一样
It was different.
个头比较大  是蓝色的
It was, uh, bigger. Bluish.
它的血都浇在你身上了
And you got covered in its blood.
确实如此
As a matter of fact, I did.
他们知道我们明天会登滩
They know we're coming on the beach tomorrow.
那是一场大屠杀  对吗
It's a slaughter, isn't it?
你怎么会知道
How do you know this?
你能不能  等等
Could you just... wait!
等等  等一下
Wait. Wait.
你能不能解释一下
Look, would you please just explain to me
到底是怎么回事
what the hell is happening?
我也曾和你一样
What happened to you happened to me.
我也会死而复生  但现在不能了
I had it. I lost it. Okay?
那太好了  这可以被治愈
I mean, that's great. There's a cure.
我如何才能摆脱这种境况
How do I get rid of this?
首先  你得帮助我
First, I need your help.
怎么帮助你
Help with... with what exactly?
赢取战争胜利
Winning the war.
走吧  快点
Let's go! Come on!
武器维修室
丽塔  他是谁  丽塔  你怎么来了
Rita, what is this? Rita? What are you doing here?
你得告诉我出了什么大事
You gotta give me some warning.
他是谁
Who's this?
他就是参加凡尔登战役之前的我
He's me. Before Verdun.
他能帮助我们
He's gonna help us.
什么  你说他也
What? You-you mean he's...
没错
Yes.
他什么时候死的  死在哪儿
When did he die? Where?
死在明天的登滩行动
On the beach. Tomorrow.
我背后伸出几根手指
How many fingers am I holding up behind my back?
我怎么知道
How should I know that?
好吧
Okay.
那么
So...
这是我们第一次对话
This is the first time we've had this conversation.
你用这个扎他试试
You should try this on him.
这到底是什么玩意儿
What the hell is that?
那没用的
It doesn't work.
他现在见过幻像了吗
Has he had any visions yet?
什么幻象
Visions of what?
好吧  看来还有时间
Okay, so there's still time.
-是的  -时间
- Yes. - Time? Look.
抱歉  这到底
I... I'm sorry. Which is...?
这是谁
Who is this?
你是谁
Who are you?
我是卡特尔博士
I'm Dr. Carter.
研究粒子物理  先进的微生物学
Particle physics. Advanced microbiology.
他也是唯一相信
He's also the only other person
你离奇经历的人
who'll believe what's happening to you.
没有人比他更了解变种
No one understands mimic biology better than him.
伦敦街道  政府机关所在地
他是怀特霍尔首屈一指的分析师
He's a top analyst at Whitehall.
在遇到丽塔之前  我确实如她所说
Well, I mean, I was until I met Rita
但现在我只不过是个
and now I'm just a...
异想天开的神经病修理工
a "Mechanic with psychiatric delusions."
卡特尔  给他看看
Carter. Show him.
是啊  好的
Yeah, right.
好了  首先
Right. Well, first of all...
你不是和一支军队在作战
You're not fighting an army.
你要把它想成单一生物
You have to think of this as a single organism.
这些游勇伞兵
Now...These common drones,
就像是它的爪牙
they act like its claws.
而你杀死的那只阿尔法
And alphas, like the one that you killed,
则比较罕见
are much more rare.
没错  据我推算  他们存在的概率为
Yeah. They're like one in six point one eight million,
-618万分之一  -对
- by my guess. - Yes.
他们相当于敌人的
They act as the enemy's...
他们就像是敌人的中枢神经系统
they're-they're like its central nervous system.
但这才是大脑
But this is the brain.
控制所有生物
It controls them all.
这就是欧米加
And this is the omega.
欧米加有控制时间的能力
And the omega has the ability to control time.
一旦阿尔法被杀
Whenever an Alpha is killed...
就会触发自动反应机制
An automatic response is triggered.
欧米加就会重置时间
The omega starts the day over again.
但是你看  这次它能够记住
But you see, this time it can remember
将会发生什么
what's going to happen...
就和你一样
Just like you do.
它在我们行动前
I-I-it knows exactly
就对我们的动作了如指掌
what we're gonna do before we're gonna do it.
-敌人能预知未来  -所以他们赢定了 它们赢定了
- And an enemy that knows the future can't lose. - It can't lose.
若果真如此
But if that's true,
你是怎么赢了凡尔登战役的
how did you win at Verdun?
是它故意让我们赢的
We were allowed to win.
它想让我们相信  我们能赢
This thing wants us to believe we can win.
它想让我们在这次侵袭中投入全力
It wants us to throw everything we have into the invasion.
没落行动不是我们的收官之战
Operation Downfall isn't our endgame,
是敌人的
it's the enemy's.
你要明白  这是一种极端先进
The thing you've got to understand is
能够征服世界的有机体
this is a perfectly evolved, world-conquering organism.
据我们所知 有成千上百万
For all we know, there are thousands,
类似的生物
millions of those asteroids
像病毒一样游荡在宇宙中
floating around in the cosmos like a virus.
一旦条件成熟  他们就会登陆地球
And they're just waiting to crash-land into a world
大肆席卷而来
with just the right conditions.
他们只需要高级生命的躯体
All they need is for the dominant life form
用以袭击
to attack and...
到时候就再也没有任何力量能阻止
And there'll be nothing to stop the mimics
变种征服世界
from conquering the rest of the world.
除非你能改变结局
Unless you change the outcome.
我
Me?
你杀死那个阿尔法的时候
When you killed that Alpha,
你不经意地进入了敌人的神经系统
you inadvertently entered the enemy's nervous system.
凯奇
Cage.
欧米加重置时间的
You've seized control
能力转移到了你身上
of the omega's ability to reset the day.
这怎么可能
How's that even possible?
也许这就是他唯一的弱点
Perhaps this organism's only vulnerability,
他唯一的弱点就是人性
i-its only vulnerability is humanity.
抛开那些不论  你现在已经掌握这种能力了
Regardless of that, you control the power now.
就像我在凡尔登战役中一样
Just as I did in Verdun.
我能重置时间
So I'm resetting the day?
好吧
Okay.
我要如何控制
How do I control it?
用死亡控制
You have to die.
每天都要死
Every day.
直到欧米加被摧毁为止
Until the omega's destroyed.
首先
First of all...
这介绍非常了不起
This is a terrific presentation.
棒极了
Terrific.
我认识将军
I know the general.
我们可以把这个给他看
We should take this to him.
把你知道的都告诉他
You just tell him everything you told me.
-他知道如何  -我见过将军了  凯奇
- He will know what... - I went to see the general, Cage.
每次都去
Any number of times.
精神病院  解剖研究
Psych ward. Dissection.
记得我说过的吗
Remember?
你们希望我怎么办
What are you expecting from me?
你有没有见过奇怪的东西
Have you seen anything strange?
他是不是在耍我
Is he shitting me?
-幻象  -是幻象
- Visions. - Visions.
你是否见过这样的幻象
Have you seen any visions like that?
当欧米加对它的能力失控时  它能感觉到
The omega senses when it's losing control of its power.
甚至它正在通过精神搜索追踪你
E-even now it's mentally searching to find you.
当它快找到你的时候
When it's close to finding you,
你会开始看见幻象
you will start having visions.
你就能看到它
You'll start to see that.
甚至能看到它身处何方
You'll even see where it is.
你见过这些幻象吗
And you had these visions?
见过
Yes.
但你最终还是看到了
But eventually you saw it.
亲眼见到它的真面目了
I mean, you actually saw it.
对吗
Right?
我没亲眼见过
Never in the flesh.
所以这些都只不过是理论罢了
So this is all just some...theory.
你也不知道这东西是否存在
You don't know if this thing even exists.
我在幻象中看见它在凡尔登
The visions showed me it was at Verdun.
我能看到它  只是
I could see it. I...
我在找到它之前失去了那种能力
I just...lost the power before I could get to it.
而当我们到凡尔登的时候
And by the time we took Verdun...
欧米加也消失了
The omega was gone.
好吧  我要做的就是等着这些幻象出现
Okay. So all I have to do is wait to have these...visions,
然后告诉你  这个叫做欧米加的东西在哪里
and then tell you where this...Omega thing is.
不  凯奇
No. Cage.
你要带我去找它
You're gonna get me there.
让我杀了它
And I'm gonna kill it.
带你去
Get you there?
我没有...
I'm not...
我都没受过专门的训练
I'm not even trained for combat.
重新装弹
凯奇  你还好吗
Are you all right, Cage?
我感觉好像哪里摔断了
I think I broke something.
哪里
What?
我的背
My back.
我现在只有嘴皮子有知觉
The only thing I can feel are my-my lips.
给我听好了  有条规则很重要
Now listen carefully. This is a very important rule.
这也是唯一的规则
This is the only rule.
一旦在战斗中受伤  务必让自己死掉
You get injured on the field, you better make sure you die.
为什么
Why?
上一次  我在战斗中受伤
Last time I was in combat, I was hit.
当时我失血过多  没死成
I was bleeding out. Just not fast enough.
我醒来的时候在战地医院
I woke up in a field hospital
输了三品托血  然后我就不行了
with three pints of someone else's blood and I was out.
我失去了那种能力  你明白吗
I lost the power. Do you understand?
-我们还是再来一遍吧  -什么
- Think we better start over. Don't you? - What?
没人知道二等兵凯奇去哪了吗
No one knows what happened to private Cage!
斯金纳  你这个白痴  他就在你旁边的
Skinner, you dumb-ass. He was right next to you.
你却说你不知道
You're tellin' me you don't know
那个小滑头去了哪吗
where that slippery son of a bitch went?
是的  中士
No, Sarge!
那行
All right.
不如我们再加五十个吧
Let's do another fifty, shall we?
开始
And one!
等下  我叫比尔·凯奇
No, wait! Wait. My name is bill Cage.
我们在沙滩见过  不  是明天
I... we met on the beach. We meet on the beach.
会见面  我拥有你以前的能力
Tomorrow. I have what you had.
好了  再来一遍
All right, let's go again.
记住  你没有时间多想
You don't have time to think. Remember.
光知道它们的位置是不够的
It's not enough knowing where they're going to be.
你得知道怎样干掉它们
You have to know how to kill them.
我只是  等下
I just, oh... hold on. Hold on.
听我说
Listen. Listen.
好吧
Okay.
动手吧
Do it.
站起来  你这只废物
On your feet, maggot!
停下  等等  等会
Stop! Wait! Wait, wait, wait!
停一下  等一会
Stop! Wait! Wait a second!
等一下
Wait a second. Wait a second.
我在想
You know, I've been thinking.
这东西能在我的血液里
I mean, this thing's in my blood.
也许我可以通过某些途径
So maybe there's some way...
传给你
I can transfer it to you.
我都试过了  没用的
I've tried everything. It doesn't work.
我是说  那个...你
I mean, have you...You know...
所有方法都试了吗
Tried all- all the options.
你是说性传播吧  试过了
Oh, you mean sex. Yep. Tried it.
试了多少次
How many times?
行了
All right.
左侧  左侧
Left, left! Left, left, le...
眼睛得睁大了
Keep your eyes open.
重来
Again.
等一下  我觉得我没受伤
Just wait! Wait. I think I'm okay.
站起来  你这只废物
On your feet, maggot!
废物
Maggot!
我已经够客气的了  废物  站起来
Now, I'm tryin' to be nice to you, maggot! Now, move!
凯奇  你还好吗
Are you okay, Cage?
当然  我很好  我没事
Oh yeah, yeah! I'm good! I'm good!
你的腿断了
Your leg's broken.
不不  我的脚趾还有知觉
No. I... I can still feel my toes.
不是吧
Oh, come on.
丽塔  丽塔  怎么回事  你在这做什么
Rita. R-Rita. What is this? What are you doing here?
这是谁
Who-who's this guy?
他和凡尔登之战前的我一样
He's me...Before Verdun.
什么意思  他是
What-what do you mean? He's...?
-对  没错  -他什么时候死的
- Yes. Yes. - When did he die?
-在哪死的  -沙滩上
- Where? - On the beach.
-明天  -我是比尔·凯奇  你是卡特尔博士
- Tomorrow. - I'm Bill Cage. You're Dr. Carter.
我们之前就有过这次谈话了
We've had this conversation before.
你在背后竖了两根手指
You have two fingers behind your back.
我看到幻象了
I've had the visions.
我看到了欧米加
I've seen the omega.
明天的战斗我们会败得很惨
It's...Pretty much game over tomorrow.
所以我们能直奔主题了吧
So, can we move this along?
好吧  在哪看见的欧米加
Okay. Okay... where?
那有个水坝
There's a dam.
在山里  我还看到了德语标志
It's in the mountains. I saw German writing.
你能找到具体位置吗
Do you think you can work out where that is?
我想符合描述的地点
W-well... I mean, there can't be too many places
就那么几个
that fit that description.
我尽量找到
I'll see what I can do.
训练结束了
Training's over.
我们明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
我们连该去哪都还不知道
We don't even know where we're going.
很快就会知道了
We will soon enough.
你现在需要想的是
In the meantime, you need to figure out
我们如何在沙滩活下来
a way to get us off that beach.
接下来做什么  我们往哪
What next? Where we going?
往哪边  快想  往哪边
Which way? Focus. Which way?
我在想
I'm thinking. I'm thinking.
-好的  -我擦
- Okay. - Oh, man!
我们上次走了多远
How far did we make it?
这挺难说的  真的
You know, it's hard to say, really.
情况...
It's...
等下
Hold!
别走
好  前进
Okay, go!
王八羔子
Son of a bitch!
我想是左侧前进  躲避
I thought stepping left, ducking...
-听好了  往左前进  躲避  -好
- Just for the record, stepping left, ducking... - Fine.
往左前进  往右躲避
Stepping left, ducking right... stepping right.
-已经说得很明确了  -往左前进
- And it was pretty specific. - Stepping left,
往右躲避  继续
ducking right. Move on.
停下
Hold on!
记住  穿过战壕  正前方
Now remember, across the trench, twelve o'clock!
然后注意右侧
Then look to your right!
你说得不够明确  明白吗
You're not being specific. Do you understand?
我说过  你得讲清楚
I said... you need to be specific.
-好吧  但  -不然我必死无疑
- Uh, okay. But... look... - Otherwise, I'm dead.
听好  丽塔
Just... Rita.
凯奇
Cage!
冲到战壕顶端
...paces up to the top of the trench.
然后我往左走
I'm gonna step left.
那里有个变种  我把它干掉
There's gonna be a mimic there, which I'll kill...
装载机爆炸
...ship explosion.
我往西北方向前进30步
I'm gonna run thirty paces northwest.
然后在战壕顶部躲避
I'm gonna duck at the top of that trench
之后往左
and then I'm gonna turn left.
我脸上有东西吗
Have I got something on my face?
没有
No.
凯奇
Cage!
我们到处在找你
We've been lookin' everywhere for you.
凯奇
Cage!
凯奇  我们到处在...
Cage, we've been lookin'...
兄弟们
guys.
兄弟们  我们今天能不能...
Guys. Can we...just...
缓一缓
not do this today?
你说什么
What are you talkin' about?
找不到你法雷利快把我们
Farell almost strung us up by our bollocks
折磨死了
for losing track of you!
好吧斯金纳  看着
Okay...Skinner. Watch this.
现在我闭上眼睛
Now I'm gonna close my eyes.
-好了吗  -好了
- Ready? - Yeah.
混蛋
Stinking bastard.
我不介意多做几个俯卧撑
I-I didn't mind the extra push-ups.
兄弟们  又是新的一天
It's a new day, people.
命运在召唤
Destiny calls.
我们只要为世界做一件事
The world expects only one thing from us:
那就是赢得战斗
That we will win.
前线传来的最新战况
我军伤亡惨重
是时候
It's about time
给它们点颜色看看了
we showed those things what we're made of.
我父亲是不列颠战争中的飞行员
My father flew in the battle of Britain.
美国佬是三年后才参战的
Three years before the yanks came into the war.
我们势不可挡  非常有种
Couldn't be broken. Backbone.
我的叔叔乔治参加过诺曼底登陆战役
My uncle George landed on the beach at Normandy.
是吗
Yeah?
以他们的战斗力  这场战斗早就打完了
In their day, this war would have been over by now.
它们到底想从我们这得到什么
What do they want with us, anyway?
那还用说  矿产
It's obvious, isn't it? Minerals.
-矿产  -没错  矿产
- Minerals? - Yeah, minerals. Metals.
-它们想要氧气  -氧气  你再想想
- Oxygen, they want. - Oxygen? Think about it.
争论这个有什么意义
What difference does it make?
它们来了  也快赢了
They're here. They're winning.
不管它们想要什么  都会得到
And whatever it is, they're gonna get it.
你不是该去战场吗
Shouldn't you be over there?
我上过战场
I've been over there.
比你们次数都多
More times than anybody.
事实上  我...
As a matter of fact, I'm...
我死过好多次了
usually long dead by now.
懦夫
Coward!
怎么了
What's going on?
停电了
The power's gone.
我找到欧米加了
I found the omega. I found it.
肯定在这  德国的卡内拉坝
It has to be here. Curnera dam, Germany.
一定是这个没错
This has got to be it.
完全符合你的描述
It fits the description perfectly.
没错  你找到了
Yes, you found it.
又找到了
Again.
不过有什么意义呢
What difference does it make?
我们永远无法到那
'Cause we're never gonna get there.
不管我们怎么做
No matter what we do...
不管我们如何精密策划
No matter how carefully we plan,
我们都无法活着离开沙滩
we can't get off that beach.
你能做到的  一定能
You can do this. You can.
你还是每天到这来  我来训练你
You keep coming here every day and I'll train you.
训练已经结束了
You already have.
我等着呢  南希
I'm waitin', Nance!
目标在五百米外  正在快速接近
Five hundred meters and closing fast!
怎么回事
What the...?!
重新装弹
Reload.
下面怎么做
What's next?
一直向前  到山顶那
Straight shot... up the hill.
好的
Okay.
中士  那个新来的家伙  叫什么来着
Hey, Sarge, the new guy, what's his name again?
我们需要一辆车深入腹地
We'll need a vehicle to get further inland.
有什么问题吗
And what's the problem?
问题在于下面会有伏击
The problem is the ambush waiting for us down there.
我们还没找到车就会被杀掉
They kill us before we find a working car.
好吧  那现在该怎么办
Okay. So, what's the current plan?
那边还有两辆车没试过
The two cars we haven't tried yet.
-那小货车  -好
- The minivan... - Yep.
-和那辆绿色越野  -好
- ...and the green S.U.V. - Okay.
我去试那辆越野  把变种引过去
So I'll head for the S.U.V., draw the mimics to me.
你去试小货车
You go for the minivan.
车子发动了你就走
You get it started, just go, take off.
-不要等我  -好
- Do not wait for me. - Okay.
等一下
Whoa... just...
发动前别忘了把拖车解开
Don't forget to disconnect the caravan before you take off.
速度要快
You are going to be in a hurry
拖车是个累赘
and you don't want any dead weight.
拜托
Come on.
凯奇  上车
Come on, Cage!
前线传回战况
On the front line.
我军伤亡惨重
Our troops have suffered heavy casualties.
敌方已突破多佛的安防
The enemy has breached security at Dover.
我没看到有
I can't see.
...寻找紧急避难场地
...seek shelter as a matter of urgency.
你呢
Can you?
变种已在朴茨茅斯  布莱顿
mimics have now been sighted at Portsmouth, Brighton
及内陆的霍舍姆出现
and as far inland as Horsham.
政府提醒市民不要外出
The government advice at this point
保持镇定
is to stay where you are and remain calm.
如果您在车上
If you are in a vehicle,
请锁好门窗待在车内
please lock doors and stay inside.
我们...收到消息
We are... are now hearing accounts
坎特伯雷及法汉姆遭到变种袭击
of mimic attacks at Canterbury, Farnham,
我们...我们  我很抱歉
and... we... we... I'm sorry.
敌方已在伦敦登陆
The enemy has reached London.
重复一遍
Repeat...
伦敦也受到了袭击
London is under attack.
开得不错
It's good driving.
我忘记把拖车解开了
I forgot to unhook the trailer.
你不爱说话
You don't talk much.
就这性格
I'm not a fan.
不喜欢说话
Of talking?
对  不太喜欢说话
Not a fan of talking. No.
不过你还是和我说了
You know you eventually do talk to me.
你告诉我
It's usually around Lyons.
你和你家人去过里昂
You tell me about the time you went there with your family.
你弟弟走丢了
Your brother got lost.
我没去过里昂
I've never been to Lyons.
你还告诉我你的中间名
You tell me your middle name.
佩顿
Peyton.
那也不是我的中间名
That's not my middle name.
对了  你在游乐场找到了你弟弟
You found your brother in the arcade, by the way.
估计是我编出来的  想让你安静些
Well, maybe I made it all up just to keep you quiet.
反正你的确和我聊天了
But you do talk to me.
凯奇  我不需要了解你
Cage, I do not need to get to know you.
如果你知道什么对你有利
And if you knew what was good for you,
你就不会想了解我了
you wouldn't want to get to know me either.
只有这样才能保命
It's the only way you make it through this thing.
那亨德里克斯呢  你了解他吗
What about Hendricks? You get to know him?
你怎么知道他的
How do you know that name?
你提到过
You mentioned him.
不可能
That's not possible.
不然我怎么会知道他
Then how do I know his name?
我什么时候说的  当时什么情况
When did I mention him? Under what circumstance?
你不和我讲话是因为他吗
Is he why you won't talk to me?
别再提起他了
Don't ever mention his name again.
-怎么了  你还爱着他  -他死了
- Why? Are you... in love with him? - He's dead.
我亲眼看着他死了300次
And I watched him die three hundred times,
每个细节都历历在目
and I remember... every detail.
每个细节都是
I remember everything.
所以我不想谈这个
So I don't need to talk about it.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
战争就是这样
It's just war.
什么都没有  我们走吧
There's nothing here. Let's keep going.
我们得找到钥匙
We have to find the keys.
弄点油就行了
Let's just siphon the gas.
有飞机为什么还要开车
Oh, why drive when we can fly?
开这玩意吗
In that thing?
让我猜猜  你恐高
Let me guess. You're afraid of heights.
我害怕会坠毁
I'm afraid of crashing.
这没什么可丢人的
And not at all ashamed to admit it.
没事的  凯奇  到时候就会了
You'll be fine, cage. You'll learn.
怎么了
What is it?
没什么  我没事
It's nothing. I'm fine.
-到底怎么了  -没什么
- What is it? - It's nothing.
丽塔
Rita.
给我看看
Let me see.
我们必须找到直升机的钥匙
We have to find the keys to the helicopter.
钥匙肯定就在这附近
I'm sure they're around here somewhere.
直升机的油箱是满的
You know the heli's full of fuel, though.
我找到了一根软管
I found a hose.
我们坐飞机  凯奇
We're flying, cage.
就算我们找到了钥匙
Let's just say we find the keys.
就算启动直升机
You know? Get that helicopter started.
可我们没有既铠甲也没有弹药
We don't have our jackets or ammunition.
再过几小时天就黑了
It's gonna be dark in a few hours.
那还不如回农舍
Might be better off just going back to the farmhouse.
看看有什么可拿的
Seeing what we could salvage.
在那里待一个晚上
You know? Spend the night there.
早上再回来
Come back here in the morning.
蜷缩在火堆旁  开一瓶酒
And curl up by the fire and open a bottle of wine.
我觉得我们该重来了
I think we should just reset.
无路可走了
Whoa! It's a dead end.
嗨  等等
Hey, just...
你到没什么  可我累了
if it's all the same to you, I'm tired.
我很痛  我宁愿重来一次
I'm in pain. I'd rather just start fresh.
听我说  给我点时间
I'll tell you what. Take a few minutes.
咖啡已经准备好了  我会去找钥匙
Coffee's ready. I'll look around for the keys.
应该找得到
That's productive.
十分钟  好的
Ten minutes. Okay.
之后我就会杀了你
And then I'm killing you.
行
Fine.
你竟然还能找到咖啡
I can't believe you found coffee.
谢谢
Thank you.
加糖  对吗
Sugar, right?
是的
Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
等等  三包  你喜欢加三包
Ah, hold on. Three. You like three.
那儿有一件衬衣  应该符合你的尺寸
There's a shirt over there. It should be your size.
我们已经来这里几次了
How many times have we been here?
几次了
How many times?
钥匙在哪里
Where are the keys?
-那该死的钥匙在哪  -好吧
- Where are the goddamn keys? - Yeah, okay.
你会开飞机  是吗
You can fly it, can't you?
不会  好吧
No. Well, yes.
是  我是说  我能起飞
I mean, I can take off.
还不会降落  所以
I'm still working on my landing, so...
那我们还在这里干什么
What are we still doing here?
你在浪费时间
You're wasting time!
丽塔  如果启动飞机你就会死
Rita, if you start that engine you die.
你只能活这么久
This is far as you go.
无论我做什么
No matter what I do...
你都会死在这里
This is as far as you ever make it.
有一个变种在距离20码的地方埋伏着
There's a mimic buried twenty yards away.
你一启动引擎它就开始攻击
It attacks when you start the engine.
带上弹药上飞机  凯奇
Get your weapon and get in the helicopter, Cage.
田地里还有更多
There's more in the field back there.
我们俩只能活一个
Only one of us ever makes it.
上飞机
Get in.
我们唯一没有试过的方法就是
The only thing we haven't tried is the version
你离开这里  回到农舍
where you walk away. Just go back to the farmhouse.
那里有一个地窖  那儿有食物
There's a cellar. There's food.
你在那等我回来
You wait there till I get back.
你会很安全
You'll be safe.
我是一个战士  我心甘情愿
I'm a soldier. I volunteered.
我不会逃避
I'm not walking away.
你会死在这
You die here.
就在这
Right here.
我救不了你
I...can't save you.
如果我去杀欧米加  你会死
And if I go on and kill the omega, you're dead.
永远
Forever.
我出事了又有什么关系
Why does it matter what happens to me?
我希望
I wish...
我不认识你
I didn't know you...
但事实不是这样
But I do.
我的中间名
My middle name...
是萝丝
is rose.
站起来  你这废物
On your feet, maggot!
你还是有希望的  二等兵
The good news is there's hope for you, private.
参与光荣的战斗
Hope in the form of glorious combat.
战斗是最伟大的救赎
Battle is the great redeemer,
是锤炼真英雄的浴火熔炉
the fiery crucible in which the only true heroes are forged.
唯一一个众生...
The one place where all men...
有事吗
Yes?
谁允许你进来的
Who said you could talk to me?
我脸上有东西吗  大兵
Have I got something on my face, soldier?
不好意思打扰了  中士
I'm sorry to disturb you, sergeant.
好了  伙计  准备上战场
All right, man, let's get this show on the road.
我也得重装上阵了
I gotta suit up.
快点  基梅尔  开始了
Come on, Kimmel, let's have it!
你的头盔呢
Where's your helmet?
我从来不戴
Never wear one.
是个累赘
It's a distraction.
你喝醉了吗
Have you been drinking?
再给我三个五五六的弹簧夹
I need three more clips of five-five-six,
八个手雷  和一个备用电池
eight grenades and an extra battery.
快去拿
Get it.
伙计
Ey! Oi, mate!
你的战甲好像有点问题
I think there's something wrong with your suit.
有个死人在里面
There's a dead guy in it.
天啊  我们成功了
Woo-hoo! We made it!
感谢老天  我们成功了
Thank god, we made it!
干掉他
Finish it!
它不在那
It isn't there.
什么意思  欧米加不在那
What do you mean the omega isn't there?
我猜它们不在那  它们知道我们会去
My guess is it never was. They knew we were coming.
它们在那里埋伏我们
They ambushed us.
幻想是一个陷阱
The visions were a trap.
就像丽塔在凡尔登的幻想一样
Just like Rita's visions were a trap at Verdun.
它本可以杀了我它但没有
It could have killed me but it didn't.
它们只是要我的血
It's after my blood.
所以他们知道你是谁
So they know who you are.
他们想恢复自己的能量
They... they want their power back.
他们迟早会得逞的
And they're gonna get it one way or another.
除非我们找到欧米加
Unless we find the omega.
没别的办法了  我们完了
The... there isn't any other way. We're finished.
不  还没完
No. We're not finished.
那个没有用  我无法让它工作
That doesn't work. I-I can't get it to work.
你在怀特霍尔造了一个原型
You built a prototype at Whitehall...
是的  还害我丢了工作  托你的福
yes, and I got fired for it, thank you very much.
话说回来  那到底是什么
Wh-what is this thing, anyway?
是一个转发器
It's a transponder.
把它插入阿尔法体内
You stick it into the Alpha,
它会用波长信息连接欧米加
and it taps into the wavelength connecting it to the omega.
这就是原理
That's the idea, anyway.
但是我无法让它工作
But I can't get it to work.
现在手头的设备根本不行
Not with the equipment I have on hand.
怎样才能弄到你想要的东西
How do we get you what you need?
好吧  这就是问题所在
Well, that's the thing.
我在怀特霍尔造了一个
I mean, when I was at Whitehall I built one.
都已经到测试阶段了
I was even ready to test it.
当我跟上级反应的时候
When I told my superiors about it...
我就丢了工作
Well, I lost my job.
他们都觉得他疯了
They thought he was crazy.
所以我们只要去怀特霍尔
So all we need to do is go to Whitehall.
还没接近大门你就会被逮捕
You'd be arrested ten feet from the front door.
精神病院  解剖  记得吗
Psych ward. Dissection. Remember?
嘿  难道你忘了吗
Hey, hey, hey! Aren't you forgetting something?
转换器需要一个活体阿尔法才能工作
The transponder requires a live Alpha to make it work.
我们不需要  我们有更好的
We don't need one. We got the next best thing.
中国代表团出来的时候
When the Chinese delegation comes out...
我们加快脚步
We pick up the pace.
带黄袖章的人总能把你认出来
This guy with the yellow armband always recognizes you...
把头低下  站在我的右边
So just keep your head down and stay to my right.
干得好
Nicely done.
三  二  一
Three, two, one.
走
Go.
一
One...
六  七
Six, seven...
八
Eight...
转身
And, turn.
好  继续走  盯着前面
Okay. Keep walking. Just stare straight ahead.
罗宾逊
Robinson.
我说了别打扰我
I've asked not to be disturbed.
最好是特别紧急的事情
This had better be critical.
人类的命运
The fate of mankind.
够紧急吗
Critical enough?
真不敢我的眼睛
I don't believe what I'm seeing.
我也见多不怪了
I've had more than my share of that.
坐下  将军  离那张桌子远一点
Sit down, general. Stay away from the desk.
如果我是你  就会听她的话
I'd take her very seriously if I were you.
不得不佩服你  少将
Have to hand it to you, major.
今天你离开办公室的时候
When you left this office today,
我从未想过你会再回来
I never imagined you'd be back,
更别说还跟我授奖最多的战士一起
let alone with my most decorated soldier.
我要给你讲个故事  将军
I'm gonna tell you a story, general.
一开始听起来有些荒谬
And, at first, it's gonna sound ridiculous,
但越到后面  越会显得合理
but the longer I talk, the more rational it's going to appear.
跟他说过会儿打给他
Tell him you'll call back.
告诉谁
Tell who?
博蒙特少将  从哈利法克斯打来的
Major general Beaumont, calling from Halifax.
他的航班因为天气原因延误了
His plane has just been delayed. Bad weather.
是
Yes.
谢谢  博蒙特  待会儿打给你
Thank you, Beaumont. I'll call you back.
明天的侵袭将会是一场大屠杀
Tomorrow's invasion is a slaughter.
登滩不过五分钟我就会死
I'm dead within five minutes of landing on that beach,
和那些你派出去的所有士兵一起
along with every other soldier you are sending.
因为敌人早知道我们的计划
And that's because the enemy knows we're coming.
我怎么会知道  我临死前
How do I know this? Before I died,
杀死了一只变种  不过这只有些不寻常
i killed a mimic, only this one was different.
它往我的血液里输送了一些东西
It passed something on to me. In my blood.
现在我不停地重复同一天的生活
Now I live the same day over and over again.
就和他们一样
Just like they do.
就像薇拉塔斯基军士
Just like sergeant Vrataski...
在凡尔登的时候一样
At Verdun.
告诉你的秘书一切正常
Tell your secretary everything's fine.
你说什么
Beg your pardon?
对不起  上校  我以为只有你一个人
Um, I'm...sorry, general. I thought you were alone.
没关系
It's fine.
她打印了一些命令  等你签字
She typed up those orders for you to authorize.
但是她忘了关于格林威治
But she left out the ones referring to the fuel dump
燃油卸除的部分
at Greenwich.
你叫爱丽斯
Your name is Iris.
九月十七日出生
Your birthday is September seventeenth.
上校私下动用了点关系
The general quietly pulled some strings,
把你唯一的儿子安排在澳大利亚
stationed your only son in Australia,
尽可能的远离这场战争
as far from the war as possible.
告诉上校他的晚餐取消了
Tell the general his dinner's just been canceled.
是刚刚接到命令
The call came in just now.
你的晚餐已经被取消了
Your dinner was canceled.
你忘记了燃料卸除的部分
You forgot the fuel dump.
谢谢  爱丽斯  你可以出去了
Thank you, Iris. That'll be all.
凯奇  行动吧
Cage, let's go.
丽塔
Rita.
-让我...  -我们在做什么
- Let me just... - What are we doing?
不要再朝他开枪了  好吗
Please, don't shoot him again. Okay?
等等  等等
Just ... just...
上校
General, thi...
这不是我们第一次谈话了
this isn't the first time we've had this conversation, okay?
正是因为你太固执了
That's-that's- because you're-you're stubborn.
你不会相信我所说的
You won't believe me when I tell ya
卡特尔博士是对的
that Dr. Carter was right.
敌人可以操控时间
That the enemy can manipulate time.
侵袭必然会失败
The invasion will fail.
不管你派遣的多少士兵
No matter how many bodies you throw at it.
唯一能赢这场战争的方法
The only way to win this war
是找到变种的能量来源
is by finding this power source of the mimic horde
然后破坏它
and killing it.
找到它的唯一途径
And the only means of finding it
就在这个保险柜里
is in that safe right there.
不管我们谈论多少次
No matter how many times we have this conversation...
你都不会接受
You refuse to accept
敌人明天会毁灭伦敦的事实
that the enemy breaks through to London tomorrow
所以我们会输
and we lose.
输的一干二净
We lose everything.
我不得不说
Let's say for one moment...
我不能合理地解释
That I can't rationally explain...
你那令人印象深刻的小把戏
Your impressive parlor tricks.
卡特尔博士告诉我
Dr. Carter told me...
这个设备需要一个活的变种去启动
This device requires a live mimic to work.
你要它做什么
What use is it to you?
这是我的事情
That's my concern.
正相反
On the contrary.
你说的这关系到全世界
According to you, this concerns the whole world.
那么  如果你相信我所说的
Well, what would you do
你会怎么做
if you believed everything I just told you?
我会找到
I would locate this...
-欧米加  -然后炸了它
- omega. - And bomb it out of existence.
你在精神上无法与之匹敌
You're not mentally equipped to fight this thing.
你永远赢不了
And you never will be.
接下来怎么办
What do we do now?
不知道  我们还从未到过这一步
I don't know. We've never gotten this far.
放轻松
That was easy.
不要动
Now! Stop!
不要轻举妄动
Stop right there! Don't move!
不要动
Nobody move!
放下武器
Weapon!
不要动
Stop!
他们逃跑了
They're off and away!
我要怎么用这个东西
What am I supposed to do with this?
插到你大腿上  马上
Stick it in your leg. Do it!
凯奇  怎么了
Cage, what's happening?
告诉我
Talk to me.
我感觉到了  它正把我带向那里
I feel it. It's tak-it's taking me there.
你看到了什么
What do you see?
卢浮宫
It's-it's the louvre.
哪里  你现在在哪里
Where? Where are you?
我在卢浮宫里  它被水淹了
I'm inside now. It's flooded.
现在我正在往下  在一个停车场里
Now I'm going down. I'm in a-I'm in a garage.
卢浮宫下面的停车场
A garage underneath the museum.
你能看到欧米加吗
The omega. Can you see it?
它在巴黎
It's in Paris.
丽塔
Rita!
转头
Turn your head!
呆在车里不要动
Stay in the car!
把这辆车挪开
Move away from the car! Move away!
你做了什么
What have you done?
你对我做了什么
你没事  你只是需要输血
You'll be fine. You just needed blood.
你根本不知道你做了什么
You don't know what you've just done.
我不能和你讲话
I'm not allowed to talk to you.
还有一个人跟我一起
I was with someone.
丽塔·薇拉塔斯基还活着吗
Rita Vrataski. Is she alive?
丽塔·薇拉塔斯基
Rita Vrataski.
求你了
Please.
告诉我吧
Just tell me that.
求你告诉我
Please tell me.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我只花三分钟就摆脱了这玩意儿  凯奇
I was out of those things in three minutes flat, Cage.
你怎么回事
What's wrong with you?
我以为你死了
I thought you were dead.
还没
Not yet.
-抱歉  凯奇  -别别别
- Sorry, Cage. - No! Whoa-whoa.
等等  等等  我不行了  我不行了
Wait! Wait! I'm out. I'm out.
他们给我输了血
They gave me blood.
我失去那种能力了
I lost the power.
我感觉到了
I feel it.
我再也不能重置时间了
I can't reset the day anymore.
我们必须在侵袭开始前
We have to kill the omega...
杀死欧米加
before the invasion starts.
我们只有不到3小时
That gives us less than three hours.
我们得有一艘直达船才能赶到巴黎
We need a drop ship to get to Paris in time.
还需要一些士兵
Need more soldiers too.
现在谁能疯狂到跟我们一起去Paris
Now who's crazy enough to follow us to Paris?
-凯奇  凯奇  -二位
-Cage! Cage! - Guys!
我们到处找你
We've been lookin' everywhere for you.
听我说
Just...Listen.
找不到你法雷利快把我们
Farell almost strung us up by our bollocks
折磨死了
for losing track of you!
我知道  我知道  听我说
I know. I know. Just listen.
你们会对这个故事感兴趣的
You're gonna wanna hear this story.
开头听起来可能会有些荒唐
Now, it's gonna sound ridiculous at first,
但越到后面
but the longer I talk,
会显得越合理
the more rational it's going to appear.
是吗
Yeah?
他知道我学校的名字
He named the school I went to.
他还说我二年级的老师
And then he tells me my second grade teacher...
外号叫麻痹症小姐
was called Miss Polio.
她不让他去洗手间
She wouldn't let him go to the bathroom,
所以他尿裤子了
made him wet his pants.
闭嘴
Shut up.
我是说
Look, I am telling you, man.
他知道一切
He knows everything.
关于我们大家的一切
About all of us.
扯淡
Bullshit.
他说你的名字其实不叫福特
He says your name ain't really Ford.
福特是你的朋友
Says Ford was your friend.
第一天上战场时就死了
Died in combat on his first day.
你顶了他的缺  把你的薪水寄到他家
You took his place. Send your checks to his family.
你这个小滑头
You slippery bitch.
凯奇说敌人也了解我们
Cage says the enemy knows us too.
它们在海滩上等我们
They're waitin' for us on the beach.
我们都会战死
And we all die.
整个侵袭就是场屠杀
The whole invasion is a slaughter.
说得好
Well, this is great.
还真是为明天的战斗鼓舞士气啊
Really good confidence booster for tomorrow.
谢谢你  凯奇
Thanks, Cage.
我们能改变这一切  对吗
But we can change it, right?
我是说  我们肯定能做些什么
I mean, there has to be somethin' that we can do.
我们肯定   有办法能获胜
There has to be... a way that we can win.
确实有机会
There is a chance.
机会非常渺茫
It's a slim one.
但是得跟我走  马上
But it means coming with me...right now.
听着  哥们
Listen, pal.
我才不在乎你知道我们些什么
I don't really care what you think you know about us.
我们才刚认识而已
We just met you.
少来 我们为什么要跟他去战斗啊
Come on why would we follow him into combat?
我没指望你们跟着我
I don't expect you to follow me.
我希望你们跟着她
I expect you to follow her.
-那是全金属...  -J小队
-That's the full metal... - J squad.
这是丽塔·薇拉塔斯基
This is Rita Vrataski.
-著名的...  -知道
- Otherwise known as... - Yeah, yeah.
凡尔登天使
The angel of Verdun.
好吧
Okay.
又是新的一天  同志们
It's a new day, people.
命运在召唤我们
Destiny calls.
全世界都期盼着我们能赢
The world expects only one thing that we will win.
今天必须全力以赴
Rest assured the enemy will thank you
否则  敌人定会感谢你
for not giving a hundred percent today.
队员们
Squad.
J小队去哪里了
Where's J Squad?
这个欧米加能控制时间
Right, okay. So this omega, it controls time.
把那该死的鸟玩意儿
Just blow the new age piece of bollocks
炸回老家  然后我们回家
back where it came from. And then we go home.
有个阿尔法守护着它
Right, it-it's guarded by an Alpha.
直接杀死它  行吗
Just kill it. Okay?
不行
No!
凯奇刚才说了
You heard what Cage said.
不要杀死阿尔法
Do not kill an Alpha.
要是杀死阿尔法
If we kill an Alpha,
欧米加就会重置时间
the Omega will reset this whole day.
我们就会忘记这场谈话
We'll never even remember we had this conversation.
它们就会知道我们要去
And they're gonna know we're coming.
那如果有个阿尔法要杀我
So what am I supposed to do
我该怎么办
if one of those Alphas is about to kill me?
你说到重点了
You take a hit for the team.
我们落地后
When we're on the ground...
它们很快就会
There's not gonna be a lot of time
知道我们来了
before they know we're there.
我们需要留个人在这儿盯着
We're gonna need eyes up here.
我要进去  凯奇
I'm going in, Cage.
30秒之后开战
Thirty seconds till contact.
凯奇
Cage!
不
Oh, no! Oh!
基梅尔  不
Kimmel! No!
福特  出发
Ford! Let's go!
凯奇  跳  南希
Cage! Drop, Nance!
跟他说  丽塔  我们必须走了  跳
Talk to him, Rita! We gotta go. Drop.
凯奇  它们知道我们来了
Cage, they know we're coming, man!
跳
Drop!
跳  跳
Drop! Drop!
跳
Drop.
你没连上吊索
You're not hooked in.
你怎么这么久才来
What took you so long?
还有其他人吗
Any others?
弹药不多了
We're low on ammo.
我带了把大砍刀
I've got one claymore.
福特  你完蛋了
Ford, you're out.
格里夫只剩半个弹匣了
Griff has only got half a magazine left
而且他走不了
and he can hardly move.
我以为你能看到未来
I thought you could see the future.
我从没活到过这一天
I haven't lived this day.
我不知道接下来会发生什么
I don't know what's gonna happen.
这不要紧
It doesn't matter.
要紧的是我们要结束这一切
What matters is we finish this.
怎么结束
With what?
格里夫连路都走不了
I mean, Griff can't even walk.
我们有三个人已经挂了  得了吧
We're three men down. Come on.
我们要没时间了
Look. We're running out of time.
收集弹药
Collect your ammo.
我们和那个金字塔之间
There must be a thousand mimics
肯定有成千上万个变种
between us and that pyramid.
那我们怎么办
So, what we gonna do?
直接走到大门口吗
Just walk up to the front door? Is that it?
我们要是原地不动  只有死路一条
If we stay here, we die.
我们肯定过不去
Yeah? We'll never get through.
我们能
We could.
用它就行
In that.
那艘船不会飞
That ship will never fly.
不需要飞
Doesn't need to fly.
只需要迅速把我们运过去
It just needs to get us across there with speed.
要是引擎没坏
If the engines are still running,
我们可以用动力杆导航
we could steer it with the power levers.
斯金纳  开路
Skinner...Clear a path.
再试一次
Try it again, now.
没有读数
No, it's not reading.
状态控制杆  降低
Condition lever, low.
主电源  开启
Master power, on.
格里夫
Griff!
我们得走了  快
We've gotta go! Come on!
我进去了也没什么用  伙计
I'm not gonna be any good in there, mate.
我给你们争取点时间
Let me buy you some time.
电源开启  肯定能行
Power's on. This is gonna work.
快点  弟兄们  我们得走了
Hey, come on, man! We gotta go!
别等我们了
Don't wait for us!
斯金纳
Skinner!
格里夫  快点
Griff, come on!
我们得走了  他们在哪里
We're good to go. Where are they?
斯金纳和格里夫呢
Where's Skinner and Griff?
他们不来了
They're not comin'.
走吧  兄弟  你得走了
Go, brother. You gotta go, man.
下辈子再见
I'll see you in the next life.
躲开  躲开
Move over! Move over!
我们得走了
We gotta go!
我们得走了  快
Yo, we gotta go. Now!
他们来了  凯奇
They're coming, Cage.
来吧  狗日的
Come on, you bastards!
来吧
Come on!
重新装弹
Reload.
它们来了
We got incoming!
来吧
Come on!
凯奇
Cage!
你先顶着
You have to take over!
不
No!
丽塔
Rita!
砸开它  砸开它
Punch it! Punch it!
这算不了什么
We've been through worse.
没事
Okay.
它在那儿
It's there.
在水里  那边
In the water. There.
是个阿尔法
That's an Alpha.
我去把它引开
I'm gonna draw that thing away.
你去杀死欧米加
You kill the Omega.
不
No.
你走不了多远
You won't make it ten feet
它就会把你杀死  凯奇
before that thing kills you, Cage.
我能做到
I can do it.
-拿着手榴弹  -我能做到
- Take the grenades. - I can do it.
听我说
Listen to me.
我们俩谁也逃不出这地方
Neither one of us is getting out of here.
谢谢你  带我走这么远
Thank you...for getting me this far.
你是个好人  凯奇
You're a good man, Cage.
我希望以前有机会多了解你一些
I wish I had the chance to know you better.
欢迎来London  少校
Welcome to London, Major.
我是蒙哥马利下士
I'm corporal Montgomery,
我将带您去布里格姆将军的新闻发布会
your liaison to general Brigham's press office.
感谢您的到来
Very good to have you.
您听到新闻了吗  好消息啊
Have you heard the news? Isn't it brilliant.
今天日出前
Just before sunrise this morning...
我们在巴黎探测到了一大股能量
A large surge of energy was detected in Paris.
我们还不知道这究竟意味着什么
We do not know exactly what this signifies.
但结果似乎是
But the result appears to be a total collapse
敌人战斗力的全面崩溃
of the enemy's capacity to fight.
俄罗斯和中国军队正毫无阻碍地
Russian and Chinese troops are now moving across Europe
行经欧洲
without resistance.
明天  我们会向西部战线推进
Tomorrow, we advance on the western front.
相信我们即将
We believe we are marching to claim a victory
为自己
for ourselves...
为我们所爱的人
for our loved ones,
为我们的同胞
for our countrymen,
为全人类宣告胜利
for the entire human race.
你们是谁  大声说
What are you?! Sound off!
是战士
I'm a warrior!
-战士的天职是  -杀敌
- What do warriors do?! - Kill!
- What are you gonna do?! - Kill!
你才没打那么多仗  福特
You have not been in twenty battles, Ford.
我也参战无数
I have too.
明天一登滩
You're gonna dump your load
你就得缴械投降  福特
the second you hit the beach tomorrow, Ford.
你们俩快他妈闭嘴吧
How about you two go get yourselves
不吹牛能死啊
a nice hot cup of shut-the-hell-up!
姑娘  你真有意思
Ha ha! You funny, girl.
你看着吧  我明天一定会创下纪录
But I bet you I set some kind of record tomorrow.
逃跑第一名  福特
Yeah. Fastest time runnin' backwards, Ford,
被自己绊倒  摔个狗吃屎
slippin' in your own shit.
停下站好
Knock off the grab-ass!
你们是谁  大声说
What are you?! Sound off!
是战士
I'm a warrior!
-战士的天职  -杀敌
- What do warriors do?! - Kill!
立正
Attention!
什么事
Yes?
你想怎样
What do you want?
我只想明白  明白
I need to know now, know now
你能再爱我一次吗
can you love me again?
我只想明白  明白
I need to know now, know now
你能再爱我一次吗
can you love me again?
我只想明白  明白
I need to know now, know now
你能再爱我一次吗
can you love me again?
我只想明白  明白
I need to know now, know now
你能再爱我一次吗
can you love me again?
我的行为无可原谅
It's unforgivable
让你的身心深受打击
I stole and burnt your soul
这种行为和魔鬼无异吧
Is that what demons do?
我的心智被魔鬼所占据
They rule the worst of me
让一切化为乌有
destroy everything
让天使如你也受尽磨难
They bring down angels like you
我鼓起勇气勇敢站起
Now I'm rising from the ground
向你发出疾呼
Rising up to you
血脉中鼓起了全部勇气
Filled with all the strength I've found
如今的我无可阻挡
There's nothing I can't do
好吧
All right
我只想明白  明白
I need to know now, know now
你能再爱我一次吗
Can you love me again?
我只想明白  明白
I need to know now, know now
你能再爱我一次吗
Can you love me again?
好吧
All right
加油
Oh, come on
好吧
All right
你能再爱我一次吗
Can you love me again?
明  明  明  白
know, know, know, know
好吧
All right
我曾告诉过你我不能
I told you once I can't do this again
我不能  不能
Do this again, oh, no